A Guide to the Rockefeller University collection of The Medical Letter publication FA241
Rockefeller Archive Center
- "Innovar Injection - A Combination of Droperidol and Fentanyl" 10:99, Issue 258, 1968 November 29 (Box 157, Folder 4-6)
- "Penicillin Allergy" 10:101, Issue 259, 1968 December 13 (Box 157, Folder 7-9, Box 158, Folder 1-2)
- "Allopurinol and the Control of Hyperuricemia in Neoplastic Disease" 10:103, Issue 259, 1968 December 13 (Box 158, Folder 3-4)
- "Fluonid - A 'New' Topical Corticosteroid" 10:104, Issue 259, 1968 December 13 (Box 158, Folder 5)
- "Suppositories for Anorectal Disease" 10:105, Issue 260, 1968 December 27 (Box 158, Folder 6-8)
- "Toxoplasmosis" 10:107, Issue 260, 1968 December 27 (Box 158, Folder 9-11, Box 159, Folder 1)
- "Pathogens Most Likely to Cause Acute Infections (Bacteria, Fungi, and Some Viruses) " 11:1, Issue 262, 1969 January 10 (Box 159, Folder 2)
- "Fluphenazine Enanthate - A Long-Acting Phenothiazine" 11:4, Issue 262, 1969 January 10 (Box 159, Folder 3-4)
- "Oral Hypoglycemic Agents" 11:5, Issue 262, 1969 January 24 (Box 159, Folder 5-10)
- "Doxapram (Dopram) - An Analeptic" 11:7, Issue 262, 1969 January 24 (Box 160, Folder 1-4)
- "Chemotherapy of Tuberculosis" 11:9, Issue 263, 1969 February 7 (Box 160, Folder 5-9)
- "Surgical Treatment of Coronary Artery Disease" 11:11, Issue 263, 1969 February 7 (Box 160, Folder 10, Box 161, Folder 1-3)
- "Treatment of Abnormal Height in Children" 11:13, Issue 264, 1969 February 21 (Box 161, Folder 4-9)
- "Antibiotic Therapy in Cystic Fibrosis" 11:14, Issue 264, 1969 February 21 (Box 161, Folder 10, Box 162, Folder 1-2)
- "Zinc" 11:15, Issue 264, 1969 February 21 (Box 162, Folder 3-6)
- "Laboratory Tests in Detection of Adverse Effects of Drugs on Liver" 11:17, Issue 265, May 7, 1969 "Early Detection of Bone-Marrow Injury Due to Drugs" 11:59, Issue 274, July 11, 1969, 1969 May 7; 1969 July 11 (Box 162, Folder 7-10, Box 163, Folder 1-3)
- "Oral and Parenteral Iron" 11:18, Issue 265, 1969 March 7 (Box 163, Folder 4-6)
- "Nocturnal Enuresis in Children" 11:19, Issue 265, 1969 March 7 (Box 163, Folder 7-10)
- "Drugs for Parasitic Infections" 11:21, Issue 266, March 21, 1969 "Correction in Issue No. 266 on Parasitic Infections" 11:40, Issue 269, May 2, 1969, 1969 March 21; 1969 May 2 (Box 164, Folder 1-8)
- "Treatment of Shock Associated With Myocardial Infarction" 11:29, Issue 267, 1969 April 4 (Box 164, Folder 9-11, Box 165, Folder 1-3)
- "Dydrogesterone (Gynorest and Duphaston) " 11:31, Issue 267, 1969 April 4 (Box 165, Folder 4-6)
- "Assay and Uses of Heparin Preparations" 11:33, Issue 268, 1969 April 18 (Box 165, Folder 7-9)
- "Norinyl 1+80 and Ortho-Novum 1/80" 11:35, Issue 268, 1969 April 18 (Box 165, Folder 10)
- "The Choice of a Parenteral Penicillinase-Resistant Penicillin" 11:35, Issue 269, 1969 April 18 (Box 166, Folder 1-4)
- "The Choice of a Parenteral Penicillinase-Resistant Penicillin" 11:35, Issue 269, 1969 April 18; 2 of 4 (Box 166, Folder 2)
- "The Choice of a Parenteral Penicillinase-Resistant Penicillin [Sources, Reprints]" 11:35, Issue 269, 1969 April 18; 3 of 4 (Box 166, Folder 3)
- "Tranco-Gesic" 11:37, Issue 269, 1969 May 2 (Box 166, Folder 5-7)
- "Nutrition and Drugs in Pre-Eclampsia and Eclampsia" 11:38, Issue 269, 1969 May 2 (Box 166, Folder 8-10, Box 167, Folder 1-4)
- "Phenylketonuria" 11:39, Issue 269, 1969 May 2 (Box 167, Folder 5-9)
- "Pentazocine (Talwin) " 11:41, Issue 270, 1969 May 16 (Box 167, Folder 10-11, Box 168, Folder 1-2)
- "Antimicrobial Prophylaxis" 11:42, Issue 270, 1969 May 16 (Box 168, Folder 3-8)
- "Intrauterine Contraceptive Devices" 11:45, Issue 271, 1969 May 30 (Box 168, Folder 9-10, Box 169, Folder 1-3)
- "Lomotil" 11:46, Issue 271, 1969 May 30 (Box 169, Folder 4-6)
- "Methylphenidate (Ritalin) " 11:47, Issue 271, 1969 May 30 (Box 169, Folder 7)
- "Adverse Effects of Drugs Frequently Used as Diagnostic Aids" 11:49, Issue 272, 1969 June 13 (Box 169, Folder 8-10, Box 170, Folder 1-2)
- "Conjugated Estrogens (Premarin) for Spontaneous and Surgical Bleeding" 11:53, Issue 273, 1969 June 27 (Box 170, Folder 3-7)
- "Manually-Operated Emergency Ventilation Devices" 11:54, Issue 273, 1969 June 27 (Box 170, Folder 8-9, Box 171, Folder 1)
- "Parenteral Gentamicin Sulfate (Garamycin) " 11:57, Issue 274, 1969 July 11 (Box 171, Folder 2-6)
- "Sickledex - A Rapid Sickle-Cell Screening Test" 11:61, Issue 275, 1969 July 11 (Box 171, Folder 7)
- "The Choice and Uses of Tetracycline Drugs" 11:62, Issue 275, 1969 July 11 (Box 171, Folder 8-10, Box 172, Folder 1-2)
- "ACTH Versus Corticosteroids" 10:62, Issue 250, 1968 August 9 (Box 172, Folder 3-5)
- "Amphetamine Abuse" 10:63, Issue 250, 1968 August 9 (Box 172, Folder 6-10)
- "Dicloxacillin - A New Penicillinase-Resistant Penicillin" 10:65, Issue 251, {more in box 150}, 1968 August 23 (Box 173, Folder 1-3)
- "Methaqualone (Quaalude-300) and REM Sleep" 11:65, Issue 276, 1969 August 8 (Box 173, Folder 4-9)
- "Fluoridated Water, Hemodialysis, and Renal Disease" 11:67, Issue 276, 1969 August 8 (Box 174, Folder 1-2)
- "A Note on Haemophilus influenzae Type b Infections" 11:68, Issue 276, 1969 August 8 (Box 174, Folder 3)
- "Mafenide (Sulfamylon) and Other Topical Agents for Severe Burns" 11:69, Issue 277, 1969 August 22 (Box 174, Folder 4-8)
- "Anesthetic Sprays and Wipes" 11:70, Issue 277, August 22, 1969 "Anesthetic Sprays and Wipes - A Correction" 11:88, Issue 281, October 17, 1969, 1969 August 22 1969 October 17 (Box 174, Folder 9-10)
- "Gatorade and Other Oral Electrolyte Solutions" 11:71, Issue 277, 1969 August 22; 1 of 4 (Box 175, Folder 1-4)
- "A Second Report on Levodopa" 11:73, Issue 278, 1969 September 5 (Box 175, Folder 5-7)
- "Bacta-Uria" 11:75, Issue 278, 1969 September 5 (Box 175, Folder 8)
- "Betamethasone Valerate Ointment (Valisone) " 11:76, Issue 278, 1969 September 5 (Box 175, Folder 9-10)
- "Potassium Formulations and Therapy" 11:77, Issue 279, September 19, 1969 "Potassium Formulations and Therapy - A Correction" 11:96, Issue 283, November 14, 1969, 1969 September 19; 1969 November 14 (Box 176, Folder 1-5)
- "Secretin and Pancreozymin Tests of Pancreatic Function" 11:79, Issue 279, 1969 September 19 (Box 176, Folder 6-8)
- "Konyne" 11:80, Issue 279, September 19, 1969 "Hemofil and Other Factor VIII Concentrates" 11:96, Issue 283, November 14, 1969, 1969 September 19; 1969 November 14 (Box 176, Folder 9-10, Box 177, Folder 1)
- "Librium and Valium" 11:81, Issue 280, 1969 October 3 (Box 177, Folder 2-9, Box 178, Folder 1-2)
- "The Safety of Cyclamate - An Artificial Sweetener" 11:85, Issue 281, 1969 October 17 (Box 178, Folder 3-6)
- "Piromen for Allergic Disorders" 11:86, Issue 281, 1969 October 17 (Box 178, Folder 7-8)
- "Safety of Hormone Pregnancy Tests" 11:87, Issue 281, 1969 October 17 (Box 178, Folder 9, Box 179, Folder 1)
- "Diphenylhydantoin in Emotional Disorders" 11:89, Issue 282, 1969 October 31 (Box 179, Folder 2-6)
- "The Use of Rubella Virus Vaccine in Children and in Women of Child-Bearing Age" 11:90, Issue 282, 1969 October 31 (Box 179, Folder 7-9)
- "Influenza Immunization" 11:92, Issue 282, 1969 October 31 (Box 179, Folder 10, Box 180, Folder 1)
- "Dip Tests for Glycosuria" 9:12, Issue 211, 1967 February 10 (Box 180, Folder 2-3)
- "Treatment of Shock Associated With Bacterial Sepsis" 11:93, Issue 283, 1969 November 14 (Box 180, Folder 4-8)
- "Methadone in the Management of Opiate Addiction" 11:97, Issue 284, 1969 November 28 (Box 180, Folder 9, Box 181, Folder 1-3)
- "Providone-Iodine (Betadine) for Surgical Antisepsis" 11:99, Issue 284, 1969 November 28 (Box 181, Folder 4-7)
- "Prevention and Treatment of Postmenopausal and 'Senile' Osteoporosis" 11:101, Issue 285, 1969 December 12 (Box 181, Folder 8-9, Box 182, Folder 1-5)
- "Antiniotics of Limited Usefulness" 11:103, Issue 285, 1969 December 12 (Box 182, Folder 6-8)
- "Medical Treatment of Peptic Ulcer" 11:105, Issue 286, 1969 December 26 (Box 182, Folder 9-10, Box 183, Folder 1-2)
- "A Second Look at Lincomycin (Lincocin) " 11:107, Issue 286, 1969 December 26 (Box 183, Folder 3-5)
- "Pentapiperide - Pentapiperide Methylsulfate (Quilene) Another Anticholinergic for Peptic Ulcer" 12:1, Issue 287, 1970 January 9 (Box 183, Folder 6-9)
- "Heat and Cold Therapy - Heat and Cold as Analgesics" 12:3, Issue 287, 1970 January 9 (Box 184, Folder 1-3)
- "Pacemakers, Artificial - Recent Developments in Cardiac Pacing" 12:12, Issue 287, 1970 January 9 (Box 184, Folder 4-5, Box 185, Folder 1)
- "Dextropropoxyphene - Propoxyphene Hydrochloride (Darvon) " 12:5, Issue 288, 1970 January 23 (Box 185, Folder 2-4)
- "Thromboembolism - Prophylaxis and Treatment of Thrombophlebitis" 12:6, Issue 288, 1970 January 23 (Box 185, Folder 5, Box 186, Folder 1-4)
- "Antimicrobials, Sensitivity, Tetracyclines, L-Forms and Bacterial Infections" 12:9, Issue 289, 1970 February 6 (Box 186, Folder 5-7)
- "Lithium - Lithium for Manic Depressive States" 12:10, Issue 289, 1970 February 6 (Box 186, Folder 8, Box 187, Folder 1-5)
- "Blood Transfusion - Adding Drugs to Blood Transfusions" 12:12, Issue 289, 1970 February 6 (Box 187, Folder 6-9)
- "Cancer - The Choice of Therapy in the Treatment of Cancer" 12:13, Issue 290, February 20, 1970 (Correction: ML 12:36, April 17, 1970), 1970 February 20 1970 April 17 (Box 187, Folder 10-11)
- "Doxepin - Doxepin (Sinequan) and Other Drugs for Anxiety and Depression" 12:21, Issue 291, 1970 March 6 (Box 188, Folder 1-3)
- "Safety of Immunizing Agents in Pregnancy", 12:5, Issue 291, 1970 March 6 (Box 188, Folder 4-7)
- "Inhalation Therapy - Acetylcysteine, Respaire and Mucomyst" 12:25, Issue 292, 1970 March 20 (Box 188, Folder 8-13)
- "Papaverine - Papaverine for Cerebral and other Vascular Disorders" 12:26, Issue 292, 1970 March 20 (Box 189, Folder 1-7)
- "Ergotamine and Preparations - Dehydrogenated Ergot Alkaloids (Hydergine) and Cerebrovascular Insufficiency" 12:27, Issue 292, 1970 March 20 (Box 189, Folder 8-9, Box 190, Folder 1-4)
- "Moniliasis - Candida Infections" 12:29, Issue 293, 1970 April 3 (Box 190, Folder 5-10, Box 191, Folder 1)
- "Hypertension Therapy - Treatment of Hypertensive Crises" 12:31, Issue 293, 1970 April 3 (Box 191, Folder 2-6, Box 192, Folder 1-3)
- "Marijuana" 12:33, Issue 294, 1970 April 17 (Box 192, Folder 4-7)
- "Erythromycin - the Choice and Uses of Erythromycin Drugs" 12:35, Issue 294, 1970 April 17 (Box 193, Folder 1-4)
- "Rifamycins" 12:37, Issue 295, 1970 May 1 (Box 193, Folder 5-7)
- "Gonococcal Infections - Prophylaxis of Gonococcal Ophtalmia" 12:38, Issue 295, 1970 May 1 (Box 194, Folder 1-2)
- "Dialysis - Indications for Hemodialysis" 12:39, Issue 295, 1970 May 1 (Box 194, Folder 3-4)
- "Penicillins - New Carbenecillin" 12:41, Issue 296, 1970 May 15; 1 of 3 (Box 194, Folder 5-7)
- "Lipids, Drug Reduction" (Clofibrate) 12:42, Issue 296, 1970 May 15 (Box 195, Folder 1-6)
- "Cancer Chemotherapy Teslac" 12:45, Issue 297, 1970 May 29 (Box 196, Folder 1-5)
- "Nalidixic Acid" 12:46, Issue 297, 1970 May 29 (Box 196, Folder 6-10)
- "A Note on Andrenocortical Steroids and Increased Intracranial Pressure" (Revision) 12:83, Issue 306, 1970 October 2; 1 of 1 (Box 196, Folder 11)
- "Diuretics - Drugs for Reducing Increased Intracranial Pressure" 12:47, Issue 297, 1970 May 29 (Box 196, Folder 12, Box 197, Folder 1-6)
- "Urinary Tract Infections - Management of Urinary Tract Infections" 12:49, Issue 298, 1970 June 12 (Box 197, Folder 7-12)
- "Blood Coagulation - Clotting Factor Deficiencies - A Correction" (12:64, Issue 301), 1970 July 24; 1 of 1 (Box 197, Folder 13)
- "Blood Coagulation - Bleeding Associated with Clotting Factor Deficiencies" 12:51, Issue 298, 1970 June 12 (Box 197, Folder 14-16, Box 198, Folder 1-2)
- "Anticonvulsants - Anticonvulsant Drugs in Idiopathic Epilepsy", 12:53, Issue 299, 1970 June 26 (Box 198, Folder 3-9, Box 199, Folder 1-2)
- "Cancer - Therapy of Common Skin Cancers and Keratoses", 12:57, Issue 300, 1970 July 10 (Box 199, Folder 3-7)
- "Thyroid Function Tests" 12:59, Issue 300, 1970 July 10 (Box 199, Folder 8-10, Box 200, Folder 1-3)
- "Diabetes Therapy - A Note on Tolbutamide and Diabetes" 12:60, Issue 300, 1970 July 10 (Box 200, Folder 4-6)
- "Iodines - Drug Induced Goiters in the Fetus and in Children and Adults" 12:61, Issue 301, 1970 July 24 (Box 200, Folder 7-8)
- "Antiseptics - Organic Mercurial Compounds as Antiseptics" 12:62, Issue 301, 1970 July 24 (Box 200, Folder 9-10)
- "Methotroxate - Methotroxate Therapy - Some Cautions" 12:64, Issue 301, 1970 July 24 (Box 201, Folder 1-3)
- "Addiction (Abuse - Overdose) Diagnosis and Management of Reactions to Drug Abuse" 12:65, Issue 302, 1970 August 7 (Box 201, Folder 4-8)
- "Propranolol - Propranolol and Other Anti-Anginal Drugs" 12:69, Issue 303, 1970 August 21 (Box 201, Folder 9, Box 202, Folder 1-4)
- "Ketamine - Ketamine HC1 - A New Anesthetic" 12:70, Issue 303, 1970 August 21 (Box 202, Folder 5-6)
- "Ketamine - Ketamine HC1 - A New Anesthetic" (A Correction) 12:84, Issue 306, 1970 October 2; 1 of 1 (Box 203, Folder 1)
- "Cancer Chemotherapy - Procarbazine Hydrochloride (Matulane) for Hodgkin's Disease" 12:72, Issue 303, 1970 August 21 (Box 203, Folder 2-6)
- "Thyroid (Hormones) Liotrix Thyrolar; Euthroid" 12:73, Issue 304, 1970 September 4 (Box 203, Folder 7-9)
- "Hydroxyzine - Hydroxyzine (Atarax; Vistaril) 12:74, Issue 304, 1970 September 4 (Box 203, Folder 10-14)
- "Sterilization - Voluntary Sterilization" 12:75, Issue 304, 1970 September 4 (Box 203, Folder 15-16)
- "Electrolytes - Parenteral Water and Electrolyte Solutions" 12:77, Issue 305, 1970 September 18 (Box 204, Folder 1-6)
- "Cephalasporins - Cephaloglycin (Kafocin) 12:81, Issue 306, 1970 October 2 (Box 204, Folder 7-10)
- "The Upjohn Company - Systemic Corticoids (See Letter June 12, 1970), Reference Material #1. Status Asthmaticus Tuberculosis", 1970 June 12; 1 of 1 (Box 204, Folder 11)
- "The Upjohn Company - Systemic Corticoids (See Letter June 12, 1970), Reference Material #2. Literature Review Shock Solu-Cortef" (Vol. 1, 2, 3), 1965 June 12-1970 (Box 205, Folder 1-7, Box 206, Folder 1-2)
- "The Upjohn Company - Systemic Corticoids (See Letter June 12, 1970), Reference Material #3. Alternate Day Therapy", 1970 June 12; 1 of 1 (Box 206, Folder 3)
- "The Upjohn Company - Systemic Corticoids (See Letter June 12, 1970), Reference Material #4. Rheumatoid Arthritis" (Corticoseroids), 1970 June 12; 1 of 1 (Box 206, Folder 4)
- "Corticosteroids - Systemic Adrenocartical Steroids Alternate vs. Daily Dosage" 12:82, Issue 306, 1970 October 2 (Box 206, Folder 5-7)
- "Lithium - Lithium and Manic-depressive Psychosis" 12:82, Issue 306, 1970 October 2 (Box 207, Folder 1-4)
- "Clindamycin - Clindamycin (Cleocin)" 12:85, Issue 307, 1970 October 16 (Box 207, Folder 5-8)
- "Cancer Chemotherapy - Mithramycin (Mithracin) " 12:86, Issue 307, 1970 October 16 (Box 207, Folder 9-14)
- "Cosmetics - Feminine Hygiene Deodorant Sprays" 12:88, Issue 307, 1970 October 16 (Box 207, Folder 15-17)
- "Hypnotics & Sedatives - Flurazepam (Dalmane), A New Hypnotic" 12:89, Issue 308, 1970 October 30 (Box 208, Folder 1-6)
- "Rubella - Rubella Vaccine Reconsidered" 12:91, Issue 308, 1970 October 30 (Box 208, Folder 7-8)
- "Drug Interactions - Interactions of Drugs #1" 12:93, Issue 309, 1970 November 13 (Box 209, Folder 1-2)
- "Drug Interactions - Interaction of Drugs #2" 12:93, Issue 309, November 13, 1970 ("Note on the Interaction of Chloralhydrate with Oral Anticoagulants" 12:108, Issue 312, December 25, 1970), 1970 November 13; 1970 December 25 (Box 209, Folder 3-7, Box 210, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Includes but not limited to: index cards
- "Diabetes Therapy - Tolbutamide (Orinase) and Diabetes" 12:97, Issue 310, 1970 November 27 (Box 210, Folder 2-7)
- "Abortion - Induced Abortion" 12:98, Issue 310, 1970 November 27 (Box 210, Folder 8, Box 211, Folder 1-3)
- "Penicillins, New (Carbenicillin) Carbenicillin and Other Antibiotics for Therapy of Pseudomonas Infections" 12:101, Issue 311, 1970 December 11 (Box 211, Folder 4-10)
- "Phenothiazines - Piperacetazine - A New Phenothiazine" 12:103, Issue 311, 1970 December 11 (Box 211, Folder 11-15)
- "Vitamin C - Vitamin C and the Common Cold" 12:105, Issue 312, 1970 December 25 (Box 212, Folder 1-2)
- "Amantadine - Amantadine for Influenza" 12:106, Issue 312, 1970 December 25 (Box 212, Folder 3-6)
- "Lidocaine - Lidocaine (Xylocaine) As An Anti-Arrhythmic Agent" 13:1, Issue 313, 1971 January 8 (Box 212, Folder 7-10)
- "Phenothiazines (Mesoridazine) - Mesoridazine (Serentil)" 13:4, Issue 313, 1971 January 8 (Box 212, Folder 11-14)
- "Cancer Chemotherapy - Cytarabine" 13:3, Issue 313, 1971 January 8 (Box 213, Folder 1-5)
- "Anesthetics, Local - Local Anesthetics for Physicians and Dentists" 13:5, Issue 314, January 22, 1971 ("Anesthetics, Local - Local Anesthetics - A Correction" 13:32, Issue 320, April 16, 1971), 1971 January 22; 1971 April 16 (Box 213, Folder 6-9)
- "Cholera - Cholera" 13:7, Issue 314, 1971 January 22 (Box 213, Folder 10-11, Box 214, Folder 1-3)
- "Jaundice - Phototherapy for Neonatal Icterus" 13:11, Issue 315, 1971 February 5 (Box 214, Folder 4-6)
- "Nitroglycerin - Disintegration and Storage of Nitroglycerin Tablets" 13:13, Issue 316, 1971 February 19 (Box 214, Folder 7-12)
- "Diarrhea - Travelers' Diarrhea" 13:14, Issue 316, 1971 February 19 (Box 215, Folder 1-5)
- "Parasitic Infections - The Serologic Diagnosis Parasitic Disease" 13:15, Issue 316, 1971 February 19 (Box 215, Folder 6-10)
- "Periactin (Cyproheptadine) Clinical Published Papers (Weight Gain Studies) ", Vol. I, Merck Sharp & Dohme Research Laboratories, 1971 February; 1 of 1 (Box 215, Folder 11)
- "Periactin (Cyproheptadine) Clinical Published Papers (Weight Gain Studies) ", Vol. II, Merck Sharp & Dohme Research Laboratories, 1971 February; 1 of 1 (Box 216, Folder 1)
- "Cyproheptadine - Cyproheptadine (Periactin)" 13:17, Issue 317, 1971 March 5 (Box 216, Folder 2-6)
- "Phenothiazines (Mesoridazine) - Mesoridazine (Serentil) Again" 13:18, Issue 317, 1971 March 5 (Box 216, Folder 7-11)
- "Alcohol and Alcoholism - Treatment of Alcohol Withdrawal Syndromes" 13:19, Issue 317, 1971 March 5 (Box 216, Folder 12, Box 217, Folder 1-3)
- "Transplantation - Present Status of Renal Transplantation" 13:21, Issue 318, 1971 March 19 (Box 217, Folder 4-8)
- "Skin Disease Therapy - New Drugs for Acne Vulgaris" 13:23, Issue 318, March 19, 1971 ("On X-Ray Therapy for Acne Vulgaris" 13:60, Issue 326, July 9, 1971), 1971 March 19; 1971 July 9 (Box 217, Folder 9-10, Box 218, Folder 1-2)
- "Cephalosporins - Cephalexin (Kefler)" 13:25, Issue 319, 1971 April 2 (Box 218, Folder 3-9)
- "Anticoagulants - Anticoagulants in the Prevention of Strokes Caused by Occlusive Vascular Disease" 13:27, Issue 319, 1971 April 2 (Box 218, Folder 10, Box 219, Folder 1-2)
- "Oxygen, Hyperbaric - Hyperbaric Oxygen Therapy" 13:29, Issue 320, 1971 April 16 (Box 219, Folder 3-8)
- "Corticotropin - Cosyntropin (Synthetic Corticotropin)" 13:33, Issue 321, 1971 April 30 (Box 220, Folder 1-6)
- "Cortcosteroids, Topical - Flumethasone Pivalate (Locorten) and Other Topical Steroids" 13:33, Issue 321, 1971 April 30 (Box 220, Folder 7-11)
- "Poison and Poisoning - The Initial Management of Acute Poisoning" 13:35, Issue 321, April 30, 1971 ("Gastric Lavage in Acute Poisoning - A Correction" 13:52, Issue 324, June 11, 1971), 1971 April 30; 1971 June 11 (Box 220, Folder 12-15, Box 221, Folder 1-4)
- "Vitamin C - Vitamin C Were the Trials Well Controlled and are Large Doses Safe? " 13:323, Issue 323, 1971 May 28 (Box 221, Folder 5-9)
- "Cancer Chemotherapy - Topical Fluorouacil (5-FU) for Premalignant Keratoses" 13:323, Issue 323, 1971 May 28 (Box 222, Folder 1-5)
- "Penicillins, New (Hetacillin) Hetacillin" 13:49, Issue 324, 1971 June 11 (Box 222, Folder 6-10)
- "Diphenylhydantoin - Diphenylhydantoin" 13:50, Issue 324, 1971 June 11 (Box 222, Folder 11-13)
- "Iodochlorhydroxyquin - Entero-vioform & Organic Neurologic Disease" 13:51, Issue 324, 1971 June 11 (Box 223, Folder 1-3)
- "Heat and Cold Therapy - Hot water for Itching" 8:50, Issue 195, July 1, 1966 \ 11:60, Issue 274, July 11, 1969 \ 13:52, Issue 324, June 11, 1971, 1966 July 1-1969 July 11 1971 June 11; 1 of 1 (Box 223, Folder 4)
- "Antimicrobials, Side Effects - Principal Toxic, Allergic and Other Adverse Effects of Antimicrobial Drugs" 13:53, Issue 325, 1971 June 25 (Box 223, Folder 5-8)
- "Blood Coagulation - Treatment of Disseminated Intravascular Coagulation" 13:57, Issue 326, 1971 July 9 (Box 223, Folder 9-11)
- "Diabetes, Therapy - Some Notes on Diet in the Management of Diabetics" 13:58, Issue 326, 1971 July 9 (Box 224, Folder 1-4)
- "Obesity - The Treatment of Obesity" 13:61, Issue 327, 1971 July 23 (Box 224, Folder 5-9)
- "Nutrition & Diet Infants - Iron-Fortified Formulas for Infants" 13:16, 1971 August 6 (Box 225, Folder 1-7)
- "Cyclophosphamide - Cyclophosphamide-an Immunosuppressive Drug" 13:16, 1971 August 6 (Box 225, Folder 8-9, Box 226, Folder 1-4)
- "Proctofoam - Proctofoam-Hc for Anorectal Disorders" 13:17, 1971 August 20 (Box 226, Folder 5-10)
- "Anticoagulants - Duration of Anticoagulant Therapy for Thromboembolism" 13:17, 1971 August 20 (Box 226, Folder 11-14)
- "Ulcers - Ulcerine and Treatment of Peptic Ulcer" 13:17, 1971 August 20 (Box 226, Folder 15-18)
- "Tuberculosis, Chemotherapy - Rifampin and Other Drugs for Treatment of Tuberculosis" 13:18, 1971 September 3 (Box 227, Folder 1-6)
- "Acetaminophen - Acetaminophen, valadol an analgesic and renal injury" 13:18, 1971 September 3 (Box 227, Folder 7-12)
- "Resuscitation - Manually Operated Emergency Ventilation Devices" 13:18, 1971 September 3 (Box 228, Folder 1-4)
- "Resuscitation - Manually Operated Emergency Ventilation Devices" (Manufacturers Replies) 13:18, 1971 September 3 (Box 228, Folder 2)
- "Resuscitation - Manually Operated Emergency Ventilation Devices" (Reprints) 13:18, 1971 September 3 (Box 228, Folder 3)
- "Resuscitation - Manually Operated Emergency Ventilation Devices" (Advertising: Package Inserts) 13:18, 1971 September 3 (Box 228, Folder 4)
- "Viral Infections - Antiviral Chemotherapy" 13:19, 1971 September 17 (Box 228, Folder 5-9)
- "Viral Infections - Antiviral Chemotherapy" (Consultants: M. L. Drafts) [II] 13:19, 1971 September 17 (Box 228, Folder 6)
- "Viral Infections - Antiviral Chemotherapy" (Manufacturers Replies) 13:19, 1971 September 17 (Box 228, Folder 7)
- "Viral Infections - Antiviral Chemotherapy" (Original Manuscript) 13:19, 1971 September 17 (Box 228, Folder 8)
- "Viral Infections - Antiviral Chemotherapy" (Reprints) 13:19, 1971 September 17 (Box 228, Folder 9)
- "Medical Equipment and Devices - Dexon Polyglycolic Acid Suture" 13:19, 1971 September 17 (Box 228, Folder 10-15)
- "Medical Equipment and Devices - Dexon Polyglycolic Acid Suture" (Manufacturers Replies) 13:19, 1971 September 17 (Box 228, Folder 11)
- "Medical Equipment and Devices - Dexon Polyglycolic Acid Suture" (Adverse Effects) 13:19, 1971 September 17 (Box 228, Folder 12)
- "Medical Equipment and Devices - Dexon Polyglycolic Acid Suture" (Original Manuscript) 13:19, 1971 September 17 (Box 228, Folder 13)
- "Medical Equipment and Devices - Dexon Polyglycolic Acid Suture" (Reprints) 13:19, 1971 September 17 (Box 228, Folder 14)
- "Medical Equipment and Devices - Dexon Polyglycolic Acid Suture" (Advertising: Package Inserts) 13:19, 1971 September 17 (Box 228, Folder 15)
- "Prostaglandins - Prostaglandins" 13:19, 1971 September 17 (Box 228, Folder 16, Box 229, Folder 1-3)
- "Prostaglandins - Prostaglandins" (Adverse Effects) 13:19, 1971 September 17 (Box 229, Folder 1)
- "Prostaglandins - Prostaglandins" (Original Manuscript) 13:19, 1971 September 17 (Box 229, Folder 2)
- "Prostaglandins - Prostaglandins" (Reprints) 13:19, 1971 September 17 (Box 229, Folder 3)
- "Electrosleep - Electrosleep & Cerebral Electrotherapy" 13:20, 1971 October 1 (Box 229, Folder 4-6)